-Art Subs-
13 years making Art for you!
Caption
-Cumby-
-willian_as-
Caption
-Frederic-
Review
STILLWATER-IN SEARCH OF THE TRUTH
What happens to the city
after we clean it up?
They will rebuild.
And will the population come back?
Most, yes.
It's crazy.
I think the Americans
don't like change.
But I think the tornado doesn't call
for what they like.
Thank you
for choosing Sonic.
My name is McKayla.
How can I help?
A cheese sandwich
with mustard and onion,
big potato
and large cherry lemonade.
We're on the road
showing to the people
the power strip-stains
from OxiClean.
Thank you, Lord,
for more this blessing.
Please,
protect always Ally.
In the name of Jesus. Amen.
You know how annoying that is?
And it can pop the eye
so.
-Where are you from?
-Stillwater.
In which drilling company
worked?
-ITA.
-Why did you leave?
The platform has been deactivated.
I was discharged six months ago.
-What are you doing now?
-Work with construction.
But it's slow
since the platform stopped.
I'm doing the cleaning,
after the tornado in Shawnee.
Running back.
-Hey, Sharon.
-Let me finish this page.
One more page.
Thank you for this food
and for all the best in this world.
Keep Allison
under Your protection.
-Amen.
-Have you ever been hired?
-No.
I had an interview
this morning.
Your mother called me
a few days ago.
She moved to Tampa.
She asked for money
or some shit like that?
No.
She asked for you.
Should call her
some day.
I already have too much trouble
at the moment.
You took the record
from my car?
Got it.
It's at home.
I stayed all morning
waiting.
I took it online.
Everything is online.
Don't find yourself a human being
for real not even if you try it.
It didn't stop them
of they charge me 23 bucks.
I pay.
-That's not what I meant.
-I know.
There's a bag on the door
for you to take.
And an envelope with photos
at her desk.
That's important.
It will be two scales.
One in Atlanta,
afterward in Frankfurt.
-Gate 22.
-Thank you.
Let's start the landing
at the Marseille Airport.
I hope you enjoyed it
the flight.
Sign up here, please.
-Will stay for two weeks?
-Yes, ma'am.
Thank you.
Here's your key.
Room 156.
Thank you, lady.
Welcome back,
Mr. Baker.
Hi ...
Hey. Hey!
Could they put it down?
I'm trying to sleep.
The music.
No, no ... English.
-I don't speak English.
-Right.
Good night.
THE LIFE WE BURIED
Baker.
All right.
-Hi, little girl.
-Hi, Dad.
You look good.
Thank you.
-How was the flight?
-Good.
Are you okay?
-I'm, yeah.
-What a good one.
Do you have clothes to wash?
-I have some.
-I'll take care of it.
They gave us
plus two visits.
The next one is Friday,
at 14 o'clock.
How is Grandma?
She's fine.
Still uses
the oxygen tank.
Still have opinion
about everything.
I have longing for her.
She bought it
everything you wanted.
Have extra socks
and a new pair of sneakers.
Thank you.
Grandma said she was going to send
a few pictures for me.
Shit. I forgot.
Bring it next time.
No, I forgot at home,
in Stillwater.
-Sorry.
-It has no problem.
I bought a Cowboys sweatshirt
for you.
This year is going to be good for them.
There's a new player.
Need three guys
to topple him.
He must go
for the professional league.
Cool.
Still works
in the library?
No, I left.
Dad, I need you to do
one thing.
Give this to Leparq.
Make sure she reads it.
What is it?
It's a letter.
Just hand it to her.
The address is in the envelope,
is it ok?
It's fine.
But ... are you okay?
Parent ... Please.
I'll do it today.
I'll make sure
of which she reads.
It's fine.
Can we pray a little?
Sure, Dad.
Thank you, Lord, for gathering us
on this blessed day.
And thank you
for protecting Allison.
Mr. Baker.
Sorry for the delay,
but the Maître Leparq
will not return to the office today.
I come back tomorrow.
Thank you, lady.
Mr. Baker, she will be
on the court all week.
Why don't you give me your letter
and I deliver it to her?
I can't.
Thank you, lady.
As you like.
Hey.
Is it locked out here?
Key.
Do you have the key?
Come on, let's get it.
Come on.
Let's get a new key.
Bell?
-Bill.
-Beal?
Almost.
What's your name?
You.
-Maya.
-Maya. It's beautiful.
It's a tattoo.
-It's an eagle.
-Eagle?
Eagle-bald.
United States.
It's a skull
with a knife traversed.
Thank you, lady.
Thank you.
I'm looking for this person,
Maître Leparq.
Mrs. Leparq?
-Mr. Baker?
-Yes, ma'am.
Just need
of a few minutes.
A letter from my daughter.
I'm sorry, Mr. Baker,
but can't answer it
the request of your daughter.
Why not?
The judge will not reopen this case
based on indirect testimony.
That's not possible.
Right.
We sold out
all possible legal actions.
This letter tells me that your daughter
did not accept the sentence.
And she must accept it.
Do you understand?
Yes, ma'am.
I need to go.
I have a full day.
Can you give me back the letter?
-As you like.
-Thank you.
Mr. Baker,
there is moment for hope
and for acceptance.
The last thing
who will want to
is to give false hope
to your daughter.
It could get a lot worse
her situation.
Do you understand?
Yes, ma'am.
Hello.
Hey.
Thank you for helping
my daughter Maya yesterday.
I got late a little bit
to arrive.
We're moving,
and we have no electricity
in the new apartment. So ...
Sorry,
i don't speak english.
Ah, yes.
The balcony. Yes ...
My English has returned.
I'm sorry
by the loud noise.
It's my friend Nedjma.
She's a bad influence
for me.
-I'm Virginie.
-Bill.
Hello, Bill.
It's in Marseille
of holiday?
-I came to visit my daughter.
-How cool!
I hope to stay here
just for a few more days,
but if you need something,
we are in the door next door.
-Thank you, lady.
-Thank you. Bye, Bill.
" Cara Maître Leparq,
" I'm writing to you
because I was contacted
" by Dr. Patrick Okonedo,
" head of the program
of student assistance
" from which I was part
at the university.
" Patrick was approached
by a student
" who met a guy
called Akim at a party.
" He told her that years ago
had stabbed a girl
" and went out unpunished.
" It must be the same Akim
that killed Lina. "
You are the father of the girl,
the American student?
Yes, ma'am.
" His DNA
must be compared
" to unknown DNA
found at the scene.
" I implore you to investigate,
" and that speaks to Mr. Okonedo
and with the student.
" I'm innocent
of this crime,
" and I have no one else
to help me.
" My grandmother can't anymore
come to Marseille,
" and you know my father.
" I can't trust him
to help with that.
" He's not capable.
" Please don't abandon me
in this horrible place.
" I lost five years
of my life,
" and there are still four missing.
" Attentiously,
Allison Baker. "
I'm sorry.
I appreciate your help.
Please don't say anything
to no one about it.
Mr. Baker.
Come in, please.
How can I help you?
I want to talk to Ms. Leparq.
It's about the case.
Maître Leparq
is not available today.
There's a new track ...
This guy ...
was at a party
talking about the murder.
-Mr. Baker.
-Talk to this teacher,
Patrick Okonedo.
Need to hear
what he has to say.
Maître Leparq
was very clear with you yesterday.
She cannot proceed
in this case.
But if you wish
a further investigation,
we can recommend this ...
A list
of private detectives.
I don't want a detective.
We already work
with the people on the list,
and everyone is very capable.
I don't care
whether they are capable ...
-Circulated the names ...
-Stop it.
My daughter
is in the fucking prison.
Don't need
of a shit list.
As you like.
Fuck that.
-Hi.
-Are you okay?
-I'm, yeah.
You took it long today.
They shouldn't do that.
Go call it
back in the exact time.
All right.
It happens, sometimes.
-I washed your clothes.
-Thank you.
Delivered my letter
the Leparq?
Sure.
And what did she say?
Well, she told me
what you wrote
about Akim
and the girl from the party.
And what did she say?
She said she works
in many cases so ...
Parent ...
Will she investigate or not?
Just tell me.
Yes, she will investigate.
Seriously?
Did she say that?
Did she say she'll investigate?
That's right.
I told her how much this
is important to you.
-Does she need me to do something?
-No.
She said she just needs to
of some time, and ...
She said she didn't want to
promise nothing,
didn't want to give false hope
or something of the kind ...
No, no.
But that's still great.
Akim exists.
-He killed Lina.
-I know. I know that.
No idea how many times
wrote and rewrote that letter.
Well, it worked.
-Yes.
Maybe God has answered
our prayers.
Thank you, Dad.
Thank you so much.
Excuse me, lady.
Bill Baker.
I called because of a list.
One moment, please.
I don't know how much you remember
on the case,
but Allison make college
here,
and that's when she met
this girl, Lina.
Allison and Lina
were ... together,
and one night they fought ugly,
and Allison went to a bar.
That's when she met
this one from Akim.
They drank,
and he stole her purse and ...
when Allison
came home,
found Lina dead
and called the police.
And they never succeeded
find this Akim.
He was the one who killed Lina.
What do you think?
You speak English, don't you?
-English?
-Yes. I am.
Shit ...
Return the letter.
Mr. Baker.
Please.
My office.
I was on duty
at the time of that case.
In the police.
Already talked
with this one from Okonedo?
-The teacher.
-No, sir.
I see why your lawyer
doesn't want to help.
A girl at a party listens
a rumour about a murder.
Maybe she'll remember
of this famous case.
Why now?
That was 5 years ago.
It's ...
It's the time my daughter
is in prison, 5 years.
She knows
of this our date?
Your daughter.
No, sir.
Are you rich, Mr. Baker?
This case involves DNA.
That is, it is two steps.
First,
i look for the lad.
That won't be easy.
People will comment.
He will try to disappear.
And then,
if I find the Akim,
i have to get
a sample of his DNA,
and use my connections
in the police
to compare with DNA
from the scene of the crime.
What's the value?
12 thousand dollars?
Euros.
Thank you for your time.
Mr. Baker.
Do you believe that your daughter
is it innocent?
I know she is.
So maybe it's not so much
to see her free.
DEAR BILL,
IT WAS A PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
GOOD LUCK IN MARSEILLE.
ORGANIZATION OF THE UNIVERSITY
AIX-MARSEHA
-Excuse me, madam.
-Yes?
-Can I ask a question?
-Yes, sure.
I'm too dumb
to discover this alone.
-I don't speak French.
-How can I help you?
Looking for a guy
who works here.
... the Anthropocene
proposes that the man
is the driving force ...
-Yes?
-Sorry to interrupt.
Do you speak English?
I talk.
I'm looking
by Patrick Okonedo.
He found him.
-Sit down, please.
-All right. I hope out there.
No, no, please.
Join the party.
And this new era
is accompanied
by a depletion of resources,
a fort
climate instability
and a degradation
of the biosphere
by the acceleration of extension
of the life expectancy ...
It's impressive, isn't it?
This is the type of room
that you get with a PhD.
Mint tea.
I want to talk to the girl from whom
you talked to Allison at the party.
Yes. That's what I thought.
Being honest, always
felt guilty for what there was.
Should have alerted
to Allison.
Alerted? About what?
I knew that Allison and Lina
slept together,
but didn't know that Lina
had gone to live with her.
I try not to be cynical
about these relationships.
Poor girl from the periphery,
rich American student ...
But I wind up being naïve.
Allison grew up poor.
She's not rich.
Instructed.
There are many resentments
in relation to the cultural elite.
But I'm sure
who is aware of this.
What about the party girl?
-My student?
-Yes.
Her name is Souad.
She is from the extension program,
the same in which Lina and Allison
were when they met.
And she heard a guy talking
of the murder of Lina?
That's what she told me.
Can I talk to her?
She'll talk to you, yes.
I'll give you the phone number.
Souad does not speak English
very well.
You will need someone
to translate.
You could do it
by me?
No, I'd rather not.
Still command
the extension program,
i can't be associated
to you.
Or your daughter,
after what happened.
Whatever it is
my personal opinion.
My daughter is innocent.
I wish you good luck.
Patricia, I'm afraid I need
of your help again.
I have to go to a birthday
very special tomorrow,
and missed the address.
-Hello?
-Hi. It's Bill Baker.
-Forgiveness?
-Bill, from the hotel.
Bill!
I was going through here.
Sorry ...
-Last floor.
-It's fine.
Hi, Bill.
Hi, Maya.
It brought something for you.
It's a robot.
A robot!
Mom, Bill brought me a robot!
-Can I open it?
-Sure!
-Hi.
-Hi. Sorry to come without warning.
No, it's okay.
Come in.
Some friends are here.
How did you find us?
The lady at the reception
gave me his address.
I need to call a girl,
but she doesn't speak English,
and it's kind of personal.
-Want me to call you?
-Yes, but I'll be back another time.
No, that's fine. Come in.
Let me just pick up my phone.
Come on.
Guys, that's the Bill.
-Hello, Bill.
-Hi.
Bill, this is ...
the cream of the theatrical scene
from Marseille.
-It's only going to take 5.
-Is that a break?
It is.
We're doing
an exercise with masks.
Right ...
Excuse the mess.
This will be my office,
but we're still moving.
Sit down.
So, who am I going to call?
The girl in the letter.
-Is it about the case?
-Yes, ma'am.
I want to meet with her.
The lawyer
is not helping?
I'm on my own,
at the moment.
All right.
-Maya, please turn on the light.
-Yes.
-It's in trouble again.
-No, again?
-Yes, see.
-Shit.
What a great deal. Got this
apartment through a friend.
I fell in love with this view,
but the place has some flaws.
It must be the circuit breaker.
I can take a look, if you want.
-Yes. Do you know to mess with that?
-Yes, ma'am.
Well, that would be great.
Souad? Souad?
Yes, hello. Souad?
Good morning.
...Bill Baker.
Bill Baker ...
No!
The foot of the robot fell.
Let me see.
Cool.
I didn't know I did that.
Mom, my robot has already broken down.
I'm on the phone.
It's easy to ajetate.
There it is. Ready.
Pra that serves a robot
that does not stand?
Thank you so much.
Goodbye.
Very well. She agreed
on seeing him tomorrow at 18h.
-All right.
-She was kind.
A little timid.
How will you talk to her
if you don't speak French?
Well, it's a good question.
I'll give it a way.
Right. I could go
and translate if you need to.
Are you sure?
I have.
Maya has art class,
so if you come at 17h30,
let's go in my car.
Thank you.
Show where it gets
the fuse box,
for me to fix
the circuit breaker.
No, it's okay.
You don't need to do that.
No, no.
-Now fell an arm and leg.
-Give me that crap. Come on.
Bill!
Bye, Bill!
Bye.
I have to confess,
i researched on the internet
about the Allison case.
It was a famous case,
at the time.
The press was ferocious, no?
Do you guys say "ferocious"?
Yes, ma'am,
we say that.
-Idiot.
-Imbecile.
People don't know how to drive
in this fucking town.
It's a crazy place,
Marseille.
But I still prefer it here
than Paris.
People communicate
with each other here.
In addition, it is cheaper.
And why Allison came here
to study? I'm curious.
-I don't know.
-Not?
She studied
at the University of Oklahoma,
called me one day and said:
"I'm going to France",
for here.
She is independent.
Yes, ma'am. It's always been.
Are you guys close?
Well, you read the letter.
And where is her mother?
Passed away. He killed himself.
Allison was raised by her grandmother.
I wasn't very present.
Where were you?
Working
on oil rigs ...
and being an asshole,
when it wasn't working.
It's not easy
be a single parent.
I usually work at night
and Maya gets very upset.
-What do you do?
-I'm an actress.
-On TV?
-No.
Theater.
-Do you go to the theater?
-No, ma'am.
-Never?
It's fine.
Thank you
for talking to me.
So, this guy
that she met at the party, Akim,
could you tell us something
about him?
She said he was quiet
and sympathetic.
Nice?
And he said her friend
who stabbed a girl
and that the police
never got him.
-Then ...
-All right.
Does she know where he lives?
Who is that?
His wife?
-No, I'm just a friend.
-I didn't talk to you.
Does she know where he lives?
-Kalliste.
-Kalliste?
She said he lives in a
another neighborhood, called Kalliste.
-Don't get me in trouble!
-I won't do that.
I live there! We don't know them!
Keep quiet!
How you know
that she is not from the police?
-I'm just trying to help you.
-I didn't talk to you.
-What is she saying?
-Nothing useful.
I'm ... the father
of Allison.
She's my girl.
Allison is my daughter.
Do you understand?
Explain this
to your colleague.
Things are like that
in Marseille.
The people
talk a lot of shit.
We don't know anything.
Tell him.
She doesn't want to help.
Can she tell me anything?
What's this guy like?
Didn't you understand?
You're already irritating me.
We're not god-hard!
Stand up. Let's go.
-Where do they go?
-They're going away.
No, no.
Wait there, wait there.
What are you doing?
Let my friend!
Souad. Souad! Souad!
Bill, let them go.
She's scared.
Afraid of what?
We're talking.
Yes, but here
doesn't work like that.
So tell me how it works, because
no one here is helping me.
I'm helping you.
We better go. Now.
Is it okay?
-All right.
-All right?
It's here. Kalliste.
That's where she said
that Akim lives.
-Can we take a look?
-No.
Not at this hour.
It's not safe for us.
Because we're white?
Because we're not from here.
And the trafficking is intense.
I have to do
something.
No one will talk to you,
trust me.
Bill ...
-what if there is no Akim?
-There exists.
Right, but they never found him
during the investigation.
My daughter
is not a liar.
I didn't say she was.
But everything I read about the case ...
So you're an expert
now?
No, I'm not.
The press
was against us.
The only thing
that mattered to them
was that Allison was sleeping
with an Arab girl.
Bunch of ...
disseminating scoundrels
from fake news.
That's why it punched
that English reporter?
I was drinking
on the occasion.
You told Grandma
about Leparq?
No. Didn't want to give hopes
to her until we knew more.
She's aging,
your grandmother.
Had a meeting
with the judge yesterday.
Was it? About what?
My review of the parole
will be three months from now.
E. .. is when I can
get out of here one day a month.
Right. What did he say?
She. She said ...
While my behavior
stay good,
should not be a problem.
I had the urge to say:
" Fuck parole.
" My lawyer is taking care
to get me out of here at a time. "
No, we don't know yet,
Ally.
-You have to keep ...
-I know, Dad.
I didn't say that.
But I wanted to.
E. .. someone from the office
of the Leparq was there.
Even?
Yes. I don't know her,
but ...
i asked her
as was going the investigation.
What did she say?
She said
who knew nothing,
but also said
who started working there now.
Leparq must be taking care
of this alone. It's a big case.
I told her
who wanted to talk to Leparq.
She should keep us informed.
You understand?
I'm going to talk to her.
It ended the time.
Right. Well ...
We see you in a couple of days.
Dad, do you think you could stay
a little more in Marseille?
Should something arise.
Yes, I can stay.
Just gonna talk
with the staff of the work.
Can I ask Granny to send
some money.
No, it doesn't need to.
I turn.
Thank you, Dad.
Bye.
Max.
Hello.
Here they are.
All the tools.
You can use them.
Bring them back
when it ends.
The electric frame.
What's there?
It's closed.
Understood?
Understood.
As soon as the oil tanker
gets the concession ...
Give it here, M. Let's go.
As soon as the oil tanker
gets the concession,
they hire
a drilling company,
which is for whom
i work.
And when we got there,
we organize and assemblies everything.
After all mounted,
we started drilling.
That's what a labourer does.
We drilled.
All right, test.
Go ahead, flush it out.
-Let's go. Give discharge.
-The discharge.
-Gave it right?
-Of course I do, ça va!
Bill, come. Come here.
Come see this.
Nedjma is a genius
of the technology.
I'm not a genius.
I'm just younger.
-Three years!
-But it counts.
Is this all from the internet?
All of this is from the accounts
from Instagram
from Souad
and of your coarse friend.
And all these pictures
are from the party.
How did you guys manage?
I created a fake account
on Instagram,
segui Souad and his lovely friend
whose name is Samira,
so I scored the party in which
Souad was when he saw this guy.
Then there's a chance of Akim
be in one of these photos.
-How is he?
-He says it's high,
Arabic and light skin.
Yes, light and high skin.
What he means to say
with "clear skin"?
This does not mean anything.
What am I then?
You're talking trash.
Let's print them, and you can
show them to Allison.
No, I'm not going to do that.
Why? If Akim appears,
she will recognize him.
I don't care.
I'm not going to do that.
I'm not going to do that to her.
I have to protect her.
I don't get it.
Why you're being
so stubborn with Allison?
We should go back to talking to Souad,
now that we have these photos.
Well, we stole
these Instagram photos,
so don't know
if it's a good idea.
-Well ...
-Can I say one thing?
Yes, it can.
Someone else in Marseille
saw this one from Akim,
or just Allison?
The owner of the bar ...
where they met.
He was at the trial.
-He didn't do anything, but ...
-All right.
What is the name of the bar?
I don't remember the name.
It was close to her apartment.
Right. All right.
So this is your new cause,
is not it?
It was already the zero waste,
the refugees and now he.
Stop, please.
What's the problem? You love it.
It's your weird hobby.
-Enough is enough.
-Ask him then.
I've talked about it doesn't matter.
Bill, did you vote for Trump?
No.
Voilà.
-I didn't vote.
-What?
-Why didn't you vote?
-I'm booked.
I was arrested.
You can't vote
when that happens.
What a great one.
An ex-convict.
Good luck.
You'll need it.
It's there, around the corner.
Your friend, Nedjma ...
she's mad at you
for helping me?
Don't worry about Nedjma,
she is usually hostile.
It's very protective of me,
but it's a good friend.
She helps me with Maya.
Where is the father of Maya?
Corsica,
managing a nightclub on the beach.
He was an adventure.
-Is that how you say it?
-That, adventure.
Does he visit you?
He visited,
but it's better when it doesn't.
What was it?
Allison lived here.
No. 21.
Is that where it happened?
It was.
-Good morning.
-Procuro the owner of the bar.
-It's me.
We need information.
Was it the owner 5 years ago?
No, we took over the bar
past year.
He's the new owner.
It wasn't here
when the crime happened.
He knows where we can find
the former owner?
Yes, I know.
He's right there.
Drinking my profits.
It's terrible what happened
with your daughter.
I still don't understand
how they could send
a beautiful girl like her
for the prison.
See all this rabble.
Some of them
sounds familiar to you?
Hard to say.
Everyone looks the same.
Does he recognize anyone?
They come here
and always cause confusion.
As if Marseille
be theirs.
We can focus
in the photos, please?
We are both equal.
You guys have the same problems
with the Mexicans.
It's an invasion too.
What is he saying?
You can look at the pictures
with attention, please?
Listen, you show me the guy
who wants in the picture,
and I will say that I recognize him.
And it's done.
And I will say the same thing
in the court.
Wait,
this is a serious matter.
But take a look,
all of them are to blame
of something.
What an idiot.
It's fine. Let's go.
-What did he say?
-Nothing. He's useless.
-Thank you, creep.
-Goodbye, lady.
What was there?
I'm sorry. I can't get it
more talk to that guy.
He was saying
horrible things.
Like what?
He just wants to send
an Arab boy for jail.
He doesn't care
with which.
Is that it?
What do you mean by "that's it"?
He's racist.
Right, he's racist.
We still have to talk to him.
No.
I'm not going to talk to him.
-He may know of something.
-No, he doesn't know anything!
Let's not send
an innocent boy for the prison.
My daughter is innocent.
Fuck. Don't believe
that we're having this conversation.
You must live
in an enchanted world, dear,
because i work
with lots of guys like that.
-But it doesn't matter. It's not right.
-I'm not saying it's ...
Everything I care about
is to get my daughter out of prison.
-Sounds very American, now.
-Great. I'm even.
And it's also a stranger here.
It doesn't understand anything.
Want to know? Get your things.
Do what you want, but without me.
Mr. Baker,
a moment, please.
You have a message.
She said you need
of more money
Because Leparq ...
reopened the case?
-I'm taking care of it, Sharon.
-Caring for what?
Nothing. Allison asked me
to deliver a letter to her.
I delivered, and now
Leparq is investigating.
She's looking for
by Akim again?
I said I'm
taking care of it, Sharon.
Who's going to pay for it?
No one is talking
about money. Is it okay?
-Bill, have you been drinking?
-No!
-Sharon, I'm her father.
-My God, Bill.
Should just visit her and come back
for home. Forget that.
You'll need
trust me.
Just enough.
I'll call Leparq.
No, don't do that, Sharon.
Sharon!
Dad, what's going on?
Grandma said you
is very strange.
I just need you to trust me,
right?
I need you to
look at these photos.
Dad? Parent ...
-have you been drinking?
-What? No, ever!
Are you drugging?
Ally, I stopped with this shit.
You know that.
Come on, look at these photos.
What the fuck is that?
Where is Leparq?
Just look at the pictures
and tell me if you see the Akim!
I think he shows up
at some.
Please, honey.
Please.
-No, I don't see him.
-All right. There's more.
There's more.
My our.
-My our.
-Do you see him? Which one?
It's him.
It's him. It's the Akim!
Are you sure?
Is that the guy of that night?
Dad, it's him.
Kalliste? Are you sure?
Yes. To there.
Just take me there.
Thank you.
Excuse me, lady.
Have you seen this lad before?
-Akim? He lives here. No?
-No. No.
Lady, have you seen him before?
Akim?
Excuse me, sir.
-Have you seen this lad before?
-No.
What about you? Have you seen it before?
-I'm looking for this lad. Akim.
-No.
-Do you know him? Akim?
Excuse me.
Do you guys know this lad?
This one? Akim?
Don't ...
Have you seen this lad?
-Akim?
-No, no, no.
This lad? No?
Hey, do you know this lad?
Here? Akim?
Do you know him?
This lad, Akim,
does he live here?
No, no.
And you -- Akim?
No.
Tchauzinho, cowboy.
A tourist!
Is it lost?
Do you speak English?
If you are looking for the old port,
is not here!
Do you know this lad?
This ... It's called Akim.
Does he live here?
Who is it? Your bitch?
The lad lives here.
It's his bitch.
He doesn't speak French,
speaks English.
I speak English.
Suck my dick.
See, I fight Karate.
It's like that ...
What are they doing?
Is it serious?
Calm, calm.
-It was him. He who started it.
-Shut up that mouth!
Who is he?
-It was showing this picture.
-Must be an informant.
-He was xeretting.
-Shit.
Do you know him?
-No, I don't know.
-Why does he have your picture?
No, I know, I don't know him.
I have no idea.
It goes, it falls out of here.
-Take him from here.
-Where to?
For the post. The post.
Come on!
-For here.
-Thank you.
Hi.
They asked
if I knew anyone.
Are you okay?
I saw him.
I saw the Akim.
In Kalliste.
Did you tell the police?
It was my chance.
What the hell did you do?
It was trying to help.
Say exactly what you did,
parent.
Father!
She wouldn't, Ally.
Leparq was not going to investigate
the case
My God.
You lied!
About everything.
-Of course you lied ...
-I found him, Ally.
I found Akim.
And why didn't you call
the police?
Why?
You let him escape!
Now he's gone!
If it was!
I feel so dumb!
You've always lied to me!
My whole life, always!
I hate myself
for trusting you!
Guard! Guard!
I want to get out!
-Ally, listen to me.
-No! No! No!
You screwed
with my life.
Do you understand that?
You understand?
Stay away from me.
FOUR MONTHS LATER
Bill! Bill! Bill.
Hey, guys ...
Hey, Bill.
Yes, I get it.
-Hi, Bill!
-How are we?
How was the school? Well?
Did everything?
Let's go. Yes, I pick it up.
Here. I brought you this.
-Maya, has to eat everything.
-No, I prefer the chocolate.
I know what you're doing,
but it has to eat the bread too.
Yes, see ...
Take it. Eat.
Will it push for me?
Right ...
Bill.
A hammer.
Yes. Very well.
Hammer. Ramér.
Hammer!
Formon ...
Form something ...
-Forhand for wood.
It's too much word
for a formon.
-Forhand.
-Let's go, erase the light
-Lumière.
Maya, food ...
Maya.
Wait. They'll open up.
That balding
will lose the dough.
-No!
-Yeah, it's how they do it.
Commercials
before the big revelation.
Come on, let's eat.
Come on.
Did you do your homework?
-Homework?
-No.
Well,
thank you for honesty.
I hated the school
also.
I hated everything.
I stopped in high school,
worked on platform,
as my father ...
I started drilling wells.
Is that what you want to do?
Making wells?
-Yes, I will make wells.
-Don't play.
It has to start as wormworm,
know ...
It's the lowest point.
A wormworm.
No, minhoca no.
I'll work in the tower
of drilling, like you.
Want to go straight
to the tower?
You have to have claw.
Do you have a claw?
Yes.
Thank you, Lord,
for this and other blessings.
Please take care of Ally.
Keep an eye on her.
We ask in the name of Jesus,
Amen.
-Skating!
-Skating.
-Good afternoon.
-Good afternoon, Mommy.
-Have a hamburger, if you like.
-Thank you.
For me?
-Yes, ma'am. It's the rent.
-Thank you.
Can pass the ketchup,
Please?
Did you do your homework?
No.
After dinner.
-Yes.
-Thank you.
Bill, she has to do
the homework.
I know. I agree 100%.
Do your homework.
Right?
Thank you.
When I see what you eat,
understand why prays before.
-How was the practice of the play?
-Rehearsal.
It was crap.
We did a lot of stage writing,
so it was a mess.
And the director is young
and provinciano.
What is stage writing?
We don't know what to do,
so we invented it.
-Legal.
-Legal Marchal.
Fall to the back,
camwhale up to the middle.
Within ten,
the clock is ticking,
the clock is ticking.
To bed!
Watch it with you?
Not at all.
Bed.
It's going to get me in trouble.
It's my tablet.
Yes, I'm using it.
Bed, now.
Yes, it's him.
It's a day out.
She leaves in the morning,
and goes back to prison at night.
If all goes well, she will have
another day the following month.
The idea is that the detainees
aclimatem
to the outside world
again.
-Understood?
-Yes, ma'am.
The judge requires a chaperone,
someone who will be
her assurance.
Did she ask for me?
No.
But you're the only option.
Right. Allison doesn't talk to me
there are more than four months.
I know.
Mr. Baker,
do not take any initiative
this time.
Understood?
Yes, ma'am.
What is her favorite color?
Color that she loves ...
Her favorite color?
-That, favorite!
-I don't know for sure.
Hey, Maya?
No.
I think it's beautiful.
Bill! Bill! Come see!
She lives in Marseille!
Loves football.
Allison is like
the state of Oklahoma.
Likes football
for real.
This is football,
the favorite game.
No, these guys
are a bunch of babies.
A bunch of crimping babies.
They're not babies.
It's the best team in the world!
It has a lot of great players:
Payet, Thauvin, Sakai!
All right, don't be nervous.
How much is it?
And we're in the middle of the streets,
and the musicians follow playing.
They do percussion
and everyone will sing with the audience.
Mama.
Mom, look!
The Bill bought me a T-shirt!
Wow! Did you thank you?
Don't ...
Thank you, Bill.
-Right
-Thank you, Bill.
-Maya, remember the Renaud?
-Yes.
-Hi, Maya.
-Hi.
Hi. You must be the Bill.
-Yes, sir. Hello.
-Nice to meet you.
Virginie told me
that you are from Oklahoma.
That's really cool.
Right ...
Renaud is a director
towards stardom.
It's me.
You are what you do
the stage writing?
Yes. You know
stage writing?
Great. You know, man,
i love working like that.
It's real, you know?
Stage writing?
It's true.
It comes from life.
Virginie has been telling me
about respect, no?
Yes. Thank you, Bill ...
Help me with the table?
The dinner is ...
-Yes, you can let it.
-Thank you, Bill.
It's serious.
Pra me makes every sense.
The people
should be able to have guns.
As you like.
It's freedom.
Fundamental freedom.
I'd love to have a gun.
You already have a trumpet!
I'm right
of who has a gun.
-Don't have, Bill?
-Yes, sir. I have it.
-That!
-No, you don't have it.
Why wouldn't you?
I have two.
I have a shotgun
and a Glock.
-No, shit. It's not true!
-Two! Perfect!
No, for...
All right, all right.
It's your ...
-It's his culture.
-Culture ...
Culture is a broad concept,
no?
I'll shut down for today,
people.
What is it, Bill. It's early.
-I'll put Maya in bed.
-I can do that.
-I do.
-Right.
You're my favorite.
Favorite what?
Favorite American.
Good dreams, little girl.
You know it's Sunday morning,
no?
Where's your friend?
He left early on.
We drank a little bit more.
Drinking is crap.
It was thinking ... Would like
of bringing Allison here.
Won't it be too much for her?
Would like her to see
where I live.
If it's ok
for you.
Why wouldn't you be?
Not everyone is like that.
Is the van yours?
From work.
-What work?
-Construction.
I talked about it
in the letters.
Didn't you receive it?
-I received it.
I didn't read them.
-Want to go?
-Yes.
Thank you.
Life is brutal.
Can I drive?
I was sacrificed by brothers
Crucified by lovers
But in spite of everything ...
I don't hear that song
makes time.
Special playlist
for today.
What age has this thing?
It still works.
When I have
That nebulous feeling
So didn't go home?
No.
Why?
But it's hard
Follow believing
I'll even go out
While the rain
Slaughter your hope on the ground
And tonight
This same fall
Are you sure
that we can park here?
What are they going to do?
Arrest me?
Olympique from Marseille!
Now you are even
a native.
Maya convinced me.
It's her favorite team.
Does this child have a parent?
He's not around.
Lives on a beach,
or something like that.
Cool.
Then this woman
is it your girlfriend?
It's not like that,
only live with them.
As roommates.
What does she do?
-It's a kind of actress.
-A kind of actress?
Is it a striper?
No!
She just doesn't act on TV
or thing like that. She ...
makes theatre.
Theater!
Have you seen her act?
What I'm going to do
in a fucking theater?
It's ...
You know what's the worst?
Never had the opportunity
of crying for her.
Lina.
It was so intense
when we met.
She was a lot of fun.
Cool and beautiful ...
Then she moved,
and everything went by water below.
She started to sleep
with other people.
As if it didn't matter.
As if it were ...
just using me.
Or something like that.
I felt so humiliated!
But you know,
the bad of truth is ...
that I just wanted to see her.
Just wanted to be with her.
So much!
-See.
-Yes.
-Ready?
One, two, three!
No, no ...
They arrived!
-Hello.
This is Allison.
Thank you, Dad.
I think she already knew.
-I'm Virginie.
-I'm Allison.
-Nice.
-Come, come in.
-Thank you.
Maya, come say hi.
Maya? Maya?
Come here.
Wait ...
I'm sniffing something.
There's a little hidden animus
somewhere around here.
A kitten?
-Do you speak French?
-Yes.
Of course
that I speak French.
So you're the famous Maya.
Yes.
What's your favorite color?
My favorite color ...
Light blue and white.
The color of the OM!
-Go OM!
Let me show you
my room.
Yes.
What's the prison like?
Nothing good ...
and very hot.
When finished,
i will do your nails.
-My?
-Yes.
So will look beautiful
for when to come back.
Hey, guys!
Dinner is on the table!
Watch out, it's hot.
-So use this.
-I get it, I get ...
It looks good.
Let's pray.
Thank you, Lord, for this
and many other blessings.
Thank you for the special day
with Ally.
We pray in the name of Jesus.
Amen.
Maya?
Digging.
-Here it is.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Then you two
are not even having sex?
-Allison Baker!
-What?
What?
You're all French now,
thought it would be ok
talk about sex at the dinner table.
It was bad.
Is that all right?
The food.
Honestly,
it's the best meal I've had
in a good time.
What a good one.
And no, we didn't have sex.
Jesus!
-Can I eat a tomato?
-You can.
Do you like tomato?
-Yes! What about you?
Love it!
Where did they have lunch today?
-Pizza.
-Pizza?
Chez Sauveur.
My favorite pizzeria.
-Is it?
-Very good.
I'm curious, why
came to study in Marseille?
It was far.
And totally different.
And the pizza ...
I love pizza.
I also like it.
He seems happy.
It's not always easy,
but the two
really found themselves.
Even?
Yes.
He seeks her at school
every day.
He speaks in English
and she pretends to understand.
It's cute.
You know ...
when my mother died,
he put all of her stuff
in a deposit.
After, when I grew up,
i wanted some things.
But when I passed
by the entrance ...
there was nothing else.
He didn't pay more
the account,
then ...
they threw it out
the things of my mother.
There's nothing left of her.
But he's here now.
Stayed to be close
of you.
Don't have many expectations
with my father.
He's a stinger.
It's always been.
It's in it.
I know because ...
it's on me too.
It's more beautiful
on this side of the wall.
I liked them.
From Virginie and Maya.
It's good what you have.
I'm just trying
do the right thing.
I'm happy for you, Dad.
-Good evening.
Permission to enter.
How is it?
Very well.
Is it?
Was the day good?
Passed flying.
Thank you.
Why?
For everything, I think.
Well ... Good night.
Good night.
Excuse me.
I'm Bill Baker, Allison's father
Baker, from Baumettes.
What was there with her?
What does that mean?
Hanged. Hanged.
We have to go now.
Sir, let's go.
Come on.
Let me loose!
You can wait here.
Are you okay, sir?
I don't abandon you,
Tu don't abandon me.
Is she okay?
It's stable.
Hi, Bill!
I talked to Sharon again,
said you had come back
for here.
The work is going well.
A good team ...
16, 17,
18, 16...
Bill!
-What, I messed up?
-Yeah, it blew it.
" Love at first sight
" I was enchanted
by the way he looked at me. "
Lumière.
Light.
Casquette.
Boné.
-Glasses.
-Lunettes.
Thanks for the help.
There's no truth.
Just stories
to count.
Mathilde ...
alone in that house.
And you --
the day after the accident,
sitting in the kitchen.
-Didn't hear ...
-Thank you, Virginie.
We'll take a break.
Virginie, it's good.
Keep in mind
the rhythm of the lights.
Right.
Renaud, I don't know what I am
doing with the closet.
It's looking for, Paul.
Want to sit with others?
No, I prefer to do something,
but that doesn't make sense.
I don't even know
what I'm looking for.
Paul, there is no answer
for what you're looking for.
There's no truth.
Thank you.
So, what did you think?
-What did I find?
-It is.
From the play, what did you think?
It was good, it's ...
Is it? What was good?
Well ...
I have no idea.
I don't know anything about plays.
-And it was all in French.
-Let's go, Bill. A little something.
No one seemed
a real person.
-What?
-It just seemed weird.
Look, certainly
was great.
Don't ask me.
I'm an idiot.
No, you're not.
And no, it wasn't great.
Thank you.
Health.
But I will say,
have you been ...
very well.
The best thing from there.
So ...
I have good news.
I got the part.
On TV?
-Yes, and I accepted it.
-Don't play.
-That's great.
-It is.
But ...
is more money,
but it's also more hours,
what does it mean
that I will have to pay a nanny,
and i will spend more time
away from the Maya.
I can help
with the Maya as well.
No, you already help
o enough.
You have jobs.
It's busy.
I don't care.
I want to do it.
Why?
I like to spend time
with her.
And with me too?
Yes.
With you too.
How much do you like?
Very much.
I'd say a lot.
It would be a big change
for us.
I think it would be.
Do you think?
I mean, I know.
And you know -- what?
For the love of God!
-All right?
-Yes.
-Was that all right?
Do you have money?
I have.
How much is it?
Sixty.
Seriously?
It's your music.
-Is it?
-It is.
Kind of sad, no?
Maybe I should ...
Hell, no!
-No, that's beautiful.
-Is it?
It's, it gives you to dance with it.
Even?
No, no, no. Come here.
Come on. I'll show you.
-Do you show me?
-Yes, I show it.
Come lie next to me
This is Sammi Smith.
Until the first light of the morning
Everything I'm taking
It's your time
Help me cross
The night
They're keeping an eye on us.
Joshua ...
-Isn't it in bed?
-No.
-Want to dance?
-I want to.
Come on.
Let the evil assume
The Tomorrow
But today I need
From a friend
Ready?
The yesterday is dead
And buried
And the tomorrow away from the view
-I need to ask you one thing.
-What?
Do you have even a gun?
Two guns.
Maya?
Can reach me
my casque?
-What?
-My casque,
my helmet,
my hard hat ...
Can you get it for me?
Tickets for the game
of the OM?
In the Vélodrome?
Yes, ma'am.
That!
I'll see the OM game
with the Bill!
There it goes!
It's him! Shirt 10!
It's Dimitri Payet.
He's very good!
Didn't play in the World Cup
because it was bruised.
Man,
the place is boiling!
-What?
-A lot of fans going crazy.
Someone should tell them
who are winning.
Right, let's go.
Bill.
Where are we going?
I think I saw a friend
of the work.
I want to see if it's him.
-A friend?
-Yeah, a friend.
Right, let's get the van.
-Is it your friend?
-No, it wasn't him.
-How's it going?
-Well. The game is over.
We'll be home soon.
-Right, as you wish.
-Is it Mom?
-It's the night of yours.
-Right.
I'll see you in a little bit.
Go back to sleep.
Come on.
Let's go home.
Mr. Baker.
-Nice to see you again.
-It's late.
I'm sorry.
What can I do for you,
Mr. Baker?
The DNA test we talked about ...
I want to do it.
First I'll need
of the DNA sample.
I can ask
how did you get it?
Can you do it or not?
Yes, I can.
But I'm a former cop,
then let it say:
it would be a big mistake
commit a crime
to prove innocence
of your daughter.
That's not going to take it off
of the string.
And will make it arrested.
Do you understand?
How fast do you get?
It's hard to say.
One week at least,
but it will cost you.
Here's 3 thousand.
Give the other 3
when it ends,
but it has to be
faster.
Even if I hit, I still have
that to find this lad.
-No, it doesn't.
-Do you know where he is?
It can disappear
before the results.
It won't.
Call when it's over.
-Don't we go to the basement?
-No, today no.
Come on.
Maya?
It's a beautiful greeting.
Did you see Maya?
I was in the bath.
She's playing football
in the yard.
Sorry for the delay.
It's all good.
Won't ask
of my first day at work?
Yes, yes ...
How was it?
So, how was it?
No. Why?
It tells me.
Bill?
Who's the man in the basement?
In the basement?
With the tools.
I saw him.
I will need your help.
Right?
Because it's a secret.
Can't count
for no one.
Neither for your mother.
Right?
It's a bad man.
Soon he goes away.
It will be our secret.
Right?
That's my girl!
Let's not start with that.
The media ended her.
Poor girl.
They turned it
in a monster.
The diabolical lesbian
American.
Bartoli was
at the scene of the crime.
It was a bloodbath.
He said, not the media.
Come on, she freaked out.
They were fighting.
The Arab girl
had betrayed her.
When you look and look like shit,
smells like shit ...
It's shit!
But the gun was never found.
The knife.
It has the triangulation of the cell phone.
What else do you need?
What about the unknown DNA? She said
who was from an Arab boy.
Always have
an unknown DNA.
The pizza guy comes into the house,
has an unknown DNA.
I don't know what you do
with the pizza guy, but ...
It was a delivery woman!
I have no problem
in arresting Arabs, but see,
the boy picks
her keys,
and he finds the apartment
how to?
Then stabs the girlfriend
and goes out without stealing anything?
She can blame the Arab,
can blame the Gaudin,
But she did.
She killed her girlfriend.
There's not what to do.
Love is that.
Shit.
In fact,
learned something new.
It helped me a lot.
Something that is called Maktub.
A nurse
spoke to me about it.
It's about acceptance.
Acceptance of what?
From your destination.
It's helping me
to stop fighting so much.
Stop questioning everything.
You simply
accept your fate
and learn to live in peace
with him.
It's a Muslim idea.
It's about ...
overcome all this ...
shame ...
and guilt
that pulls you down,
and keep it that way,
and makes it feel like
so impotent.
And it's how I felt
for a long time.
Impotent and forgetful.
E. ..
that makes life
very difficult.
You know what I mean?
But ... you're innocent.
So we have
that keep fighting.
No matter
that I am innocent, father.
It is not about justice,
but of finding peace.
Please listen to me.
Just listen to me.
I'm not a bad guy.
Let me go.
It's not my fault.
I don't know what you're saying,
but it's wasting
your breath.
Let's wait for DNA,
and then we'll know.
She asked me.
She paid me!
Want more water?
Allison, she said:
" Go. Put Lina out. "
-"Cash for you."
-Enough is enough!
She told me "take this."
It gave me a necklace.
" Take this.
Money after. "
Here ... Drink this.
Come on.
A necklace.
"Take it for you."
Necklace. Golden.
Like this one. Like this one.
The necklace?
I don't want that.
No!
She gave it to me.
She said,
" Go. Put Lina out.
" Necklace now.
Money after. "
It's not making sense.
Time to shut up.
Stillwater!
What did you say?
The necklace.
He says Stillwater.
Golden.
She said ...
" Do it.
Make her go away.
"Make her out."
Where was it?
I went back walking
of Baumettes.
We have to go see Isabelle.
Let's be late
if we don't go out now.
I -- do I have to go?
Yes, of course.
I said you would.
Come on.
Hurry, please.
Maya, honey, calce the shoes.
Come on!
Yes, Mommy.
So, Isabelle is a species
of godmother to us.
Maya loves her.
You'll see.
This is even the other side
from Marseille.
Marraine!
Don't know
of what you're talking about.
The golden necklace that I gave her
on the day he left.
It Said Stillwater in it.
Yeah, I remember that.
What does it have?
Remember if she wore it
at the trial?
Was she still with him?
In what is meted out
Bill?
When we got her things,
did you see him?
I don't know. I don't remember.
Why?
I'll talk to you later, Sharon.
Bye.
All right?
Yes ... Everything.
It was talking
with Sharon.
Is she okay?
-Yes, she's fine
What about you?
What do you mean?
You seem distracted.
I'm sorry.
I'm glad you're here.
Me too.
You too?
Are you happy to be here?
I am.
Seriously.
Me too.
I like you, Bill Baker.
Come on.
Mr. Dirosa,
here is Bill Baker.
Need even
of that result.
It's kind of urgent.
Good morning, madame.
Good morning.
I'm from the department
of construction.
It's about a crack
on the facade.
Thought it might come
of the subsoil.
Noticed something unfussy about there
recently.
Unfussy? In the basement?
Anything.
A noise, an odor?
-Should I worry?
-No, no ...
It's just routine check-up.
Do you use the basement?
Me? No.
Some other person in the building,
maybe?
I can find out and call,
if you give me your card.
It will not be necessary.
You helped a lot, madame.
-Have a good day.
-Bye.
You know, I also used to fight
at school when he was a child.
But that's not good.
Fight? No!
It's not good.
Are you sure
of who doesn't want to?
The man in the basement ...
Will you kill him?
What? No!
Of course not!
Listen.
Would ever do something to hurt
you and your mother. Ever.
Ever.
Because I love you both.
Very much.
Love.
Just need to trust me.
Right?
Right.
Mr. Baker,
a word, please.
Police.
I can see your identity,
Please?
Your identity,
Mr. Baker.
Thank you.
Take off your cap.
Right. Thank you.
Well, Mr. Baker,
my colleagues will take the little girl
to the inside.
Right?
-No, Bill.
-All right, all right ...
It's all good.
All right.
-Go with her.
-No.
It's going to be all right.
All right.
It's all good.
Mr. Baker,
look at me.
Do you have a basement here?
Yes or no?
-Yes, sir.
-Right.
Give me the keys, please.
I'll check it.
-All right.
-Please.
Stop it.
I'll check it.
Nothing.
Stop it.
Has a padlock
in the latter.
Do you have the key?
Mr. Baker.
It's with him.
It's in the locksmith.
I didn't find anything.
Let's go up.
Sit down.
We vasculate.
We found nothing.
She said
who doesn't know anything.
If it matters if we interrogate
your daughter?
Yeah, I care.
She's 9 years old.
Prefer
come to the police station?
Is it Maya?
Come on.
Go, baby.
Bill lives here, with you
and your mother? Is that it?
Look at me.
Yes.
Is he nice to you?
Have you been in the basement?
Yes.
What do you do there?
We organize the tools.
I teach French for the Bill.
And when it was the last time
who has been in the basement?
Yesterday.
Yesterday?
And was everything normal?
You know Allison,
the daughter of the Bill?
Yes. She's in prison.
Doesn't want the Bill
go to prison, no?
No.
-Why do you like him?
-Yes.
Now listen well ...
If you lie to me,
i'll know.
And I'll have to put the Bill
in prison.
Did you understand?
Let me repeat
the question.
When it was in the basement
the last time?
Yesterday.
Right. Come on.
Did you let go of him? The man?
Go to your room.
Go!
-Virginie, I didn't want to ...
-How did you find it?
Pure chance.
In the football game.
With Maya?
Did you ask her to lie?
Did you ask?
Never wanted to involve you
or Maya.
-I know ...
-You ...
You have to go now.
Right. Pack your bags.
You go away.
Can I come in?
Maya?
Don't want to talk to me?
All right.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I love you.
Bill!
Don't ...
Go give bye to the Bill!
Go, Maya, go!
Mr. Baker,
i have news
extraordinary.
The judge in your daughter's case
called me this morning
New evidence has emerged.
It looks like a cop
retired
appeared with a combination
for the unknown DNA.
Also combines with a sample
that the police have collected
of a robbery
four years ago,
after the trial.
Got him?
No, not yet.
But everything we need to prove
is the sufficient doubt.
So, even if they don't find it
the suspect,
there is a real chance
that they let go of Allison.
In fact, the judge has already agreed
in reopening the investigation,
which is almost a miracle.
I think that just happens
in Marseille.
Thank you for coming to tell me,
lady.
Mr. Baker, this is the best
result possible
for your family.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Thank you, lady.
Go, Pokes!
I said we would bring
our girl home,
and it was exactly
what we did.
Welcome to the home, Allison.
Welcome back
the Oklahoma.
to America!
Is it being antisocial?
Are you okay?
On the day he left
for Marseille,
Sharon and I took her
to the airport and ...
when we got there,
was ashamed for not having
a gift or nothing, so ...
i went
up to the gift shop.
I thought I'd buy you a book,
a locksmith or anything.
So I saw this necklace.
I thought it would be a bit of a little bit
from home to take with you.
It was golden.
It Said Stillwater in it.
Didn't want
that that happened.
He said he would only help me
taking her out of the apartment.
Didn't want
that she died.
I loved her.
I know I do.
Think I'm a monster?
You're my daughter.
I --
could ever find that.
Dad, what's wrong
with us?
I don't know, little girl.
I don't know.
I'm sorry. Much!
I'm sorry.
Me too.
Take the ribbon out of my hair
Shake it and drop it
Put it gently
About your skin
Like the shadows on the wall
Good morning.
I couldn't sleep.
I went hiking, and ...
ended up here.
Glad you did that.
Do you miss them?
I feel.
Can you go back?
No, I can't.
But it was good.
It doesn't change that.
Sorry.
Life is brutal.
Everything looks equal here.
Nothing has changed.
Don't you think?
No, Ally, I don't think so.
Everything looks different
for me.
I can hardly recognize it.
-Art Subs-
13 years making Art for you!
Short us on the Face:
-facebook.com/ArtSubs
And follow us on Insta:
-instagram.com/ArtSubs_Legendas